Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for?
There's always room for you!
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise!
We are
So, you are alive.
The unrivaled pirate captain
who was also the ship's cook.
Yes, that's right.
I'm still alive.
But what has any of
this got to do with you?
I haven't been a pirate
for many years now.
I chose the life of a cook.
Chose the life of a cook, huh?
Yeah, right.
You didn't have a choice, old man.
You live as a cook because the only
thing you can be now is a cook.
He was known far and wide.
Redfoot Seth was a master of deadly
kicks who never used his hands in battle.
It was said that with his
mighty legs he could crush
bedrock to sand and leave
footprints on solid steel.
Redfoot referred to his boots,
which became soaked in the blood of
his enemies as he kicked them down.
You know, it really is a pity that you no
longer have that precious leg of yours.
I heard that rumor some time ago.
How unlucky for you to have
such an accident at sea.
Now that your greatest weapon has been
sacrificed to the sea, you're defenseless,
completely unable to fight.
I don't need to fight anymore.
I'm a cook, and as long as I have my
two hands for that, I'll be just fine.
Enough chit-chat.
Let's get to the point.
What do you want from me?
Redfoot,
you're the man who sold
the perilous waters
of the Grand Line and came back unscathed.
There should be a logbook detailing your
tactics, a full year of your journey there.
Give it to me, now!
Whoa!
So is he saying you've been
to the Grand Line too, Pops?
Yeah.
My logbook, huh?
You're right.
I do indeed have a record of my travels.
But I will never hand it over to you.
You ignorant brute.
That logbook is sacred to me.
It's the pride of the
crewman that I sailed with.
It's far too important to give to you.
Right?
I'll take it.
Yes, it's true that
the Grand Line beat me.
Still, I will never give up on it.
I am Don Krieg.
In the end, it's just another ocean.
I had enough weapons,
and men, and ambition.
Regrettably, the only thing
I lacked was information.
I just didn't know enough.
But now I'll fix all that.
Once I have your logbook,
I'll form another pirate fleet
and seize the legendary One Piece.
Then I will stand as ruler
of this great pirate era!
Now hold on!
It's me who's gonna be
King of the Pirates!
Huh? Choreboy?
Wait!
Don't be such an idiot!
You better back off, Choreboy! No way!
Not from this!
Did you say something, kid?
I won't allow that kind of
stupidity again! Oh yeah?
Well, stupid or not, I'm just
stating the facts like they are!
This isn't a game.
Yeah, I know.
I'm still gonna conquer the Grand Line.
No, you won't!
It's true that we didn't have
the information we needed,
but my fleet of 5,000 men was wiped
out in just seven days, you brat!
That sea is hell!
What? One week?
Dawn Creek's ships were
wiped out in seven days?
What happened up there?
Unfortunately, I don't find your
smart-ass remarks very amusing.
If you insist on this foolish behavior,
I'll crush you right here and right now.
Go ahead if you can.
I can and I will.
It would be my pleasure to send you
to an early grave, you cocky runt.
What's going on, Luffy?
You need a hand?
If you don't need help, that's okay, too.
Oh, hey, guys.
Appreciate the offer, but I
think I can handle this clown.
Oh, too bad.
Are those two guys your crew?
That's a pretty small
group you got there, kid.
Well, that's not all.
I got two more.
I'm not a part of your crew.
I'll deal with you later.
Right now, I'm going to go feed my men.
Those of you who don't
wish to die can leave
the restaurant now and escape that fate.
The only things I'm after are
the logbook and this ship.
However if you wish to
stay and be slaughtered I
have no problem burying
every last one of you at sea.
Know that.
I'm so sorry, Sanji.
I never thought it would be this way.
You have nothing to apologize for, sailor.
Every cook at this restaurant
did what they thought was right.
That's all there is to
say about that. But boss!
Why are you acting as if
you're taking Sanji's side?
This mess is his fault! He's right!
Sanji is responsible for
this whole damn thing!
Yeah, boss, that man's gonna put your
precious restaurant out of business!
You fools don't know what
you're talking about!
None of you have any idea what it's
like to be on the brink of starvation.
To have no food or
water on the open ocean.
There is no way you could possibly understand
what a terrifying prospect that is.
It's the most difficult
situation a man could ever face!
What?
I don't know what you're
talking about, Chef Zef.
If all you're gonna do is
stand around grumbling,
then leave this place and never come back!
I, for one, am gonna stay and fight!
I couldn't live with myself if I
accepted defeat! I'm staying, too!
After all, this is our
restaurant, isn't it?
That's right, and this
place is all I've got, too.
What are you doing?
You saw how powerful Dawn is, right?
Hey, Ginny, listen up, because
I'm only going to say this once.
Feeding someone who's hungry
is my sacred moral duty.
But!
Now that your crew is well fed,
I have no obligation to them.
With a clean conscience, I can beat
every last one of them to a bloody pulp.
If anyone tries to take the
restaurant, they're dead.
I'll kill them without
a moment's hesitation.
Got that.
Ha!
You're a real head case, Sanji.
Letting him live, then
threatening to kill him?
Can it cook?
See?
This guy's awesome, huh?
Who cares how awesome he is?
We gotta get out of here right now!
Easy there, Luffy.
It is Don Krieg, but
he's in pretty sad shape.
Hey, Ginny!
You said you didn't know
anything about the Grand Line,
but I thought you'd been there.
That doesn't make any sense.
Nothing makes any sense now what
happened to us on the seventh
day of our journey through that
cursed sea I don't know if it was a
dream or reality I saw things that
I can't bring myself to believe
I know in my heart that it's
impossible for that entire 50 ship fleet
To be completely
eradicated by a single man.
It all happened so fast.
As soon as this man appeared,
he began to systematically sink
our ships one after another.
If that raging storm hadn't
come upon us when it did,
then that monster would have
destroyed our flagship as well.
I don't know if a single
other ship made it out.
It all seems like a terrible
nightmare burned into my memory.
I just want to forget.
His eyes, they were like a
hawk's, sharp and murderous.
His gaze alone felt like
the cold hand of death.
Huh?
What did he just say?
Well then, that can only be
the one known as Hawkeye.
Your description of his heartless gaze isn't
proof of his identity in and of itself.
But the way he so easily decimated your
fleet confirms without
a doubt that it's him!
Hawkeye, Mihawk
So you know him, Zoro?
Yeah, i do.
He's the man i've been looking for.
Could that man have had some kind
of score to settle with you guys?
We didn't do anything to him.
Perhaps you disturbed him during a nap.
Stupid cook!
Why would he destroy an entire
fleet for something so trivial?
There's no reason to shout.
It's just an example.
I thought you might like a little friendly
advice on what kind of a
place the Grand Line is.
And what kind of place is that?
He probably means that
anything can happen there.
Hey, Luffy, do we really,
really have to go there?
Luffy?
Hey, Luffy?
That's so awesome!
This is gonna be such a blast!
Do you understand the concept of danger?
Finally, my life's goal will be
achieved on the Grand Line. What?
My rival.
He's out there somewhere,
and I'm gonna find him.
Are you that stupid?
It's idiots like you
guys that end up dead.
That may be true, but
lay off the name-calling.
I devoted my entire life to becoming
the world's greatest swordsman.
I made my choice, so I'm the only
one who gets to call me stupid.
Hey, what about me?
Me too, right?
I mean, it only seems fair.
Shut up, stupid.
What morons.
Enough!
Do any of you maggots understand
the current situation?
That enormous galleon moored
in front of our dear little
restaurant is none other
than Don Creek's flagship.
So why don't we check back into
reality and deal with this?
Yeah!
We're saved!
I can't believe it! We're alive!
It's like a tree!
Fire is finally over!
We sailed into the pirate
graveyard, but we can't...
Hmm. That's right.
And I'm glad you all made it,
because I'll need a healthy crew
to go back to the Grand Line.
Hey, why the long faces?
Sir, why are we going back there?
Point taken.
Are there any other objections?
First we need to take over
that floating restaurant.
Then we can abandon the wreck
we're on before it falls apart.
Don't worry about the enemy.
They're just a bunch of prissy cooks.
It won't take much to crush them.
Attack!
Hear that?
They're gonna be here soon!
The restaurant is ours, and I'll fight
to the death to keep it that way!
What's going on?
The main ship, it was cut!
It was cut?
What do you mean cut?
Something sliced up the scallion?
No way!
It can't be!
That's impossible!
Trouble!
Raise the anchor or we'll sink
along with them! Yes, sir!
Wait!
Nami and the guys are still
on our ship out there!
I hope it's not too late!
Hey!
Big bro! Big bro! Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you okay?
What happened to the ship?
Where's Nami?
Is she okay?
I'm sorry, Big bro!
I don't know how to say
this, but she's gone!
See ya!
Oh, and make sure to tell them!
Big sis Nami!
If it's meant to be,
I'll see them real soon!
She took all the treasure and sailed away!
She did worse!
That man is...
What did you say? For real?
Nami sailed off with the going Mary?
I need a straight answer.
Now what happened?
Well, it all happened
in only a few minutes.
Hey, what's the matter, Big Sis?
Say, I don't really mean to pry it
or anything, but what you looking at?
Oh, well, it's nothing, really. Nice.
Now that's a big bounty pirate.
I gotta say, I'm impressed.
But Big Sis, I think you're aiming a
little too high going after Arlong.
I'm not kidding, that
guy's really bad news.
He was playing it cool and
laying low for a while.
You know, staying out of sight.
But these days, that maniac is
causing all sorts of trouble.
It's kind of tough walking away from
a 20 million berry bounty though.
That guy is so powerful
that there's the slightest
tiniest chance that we
could lose and we'll die!
Hey,
would you guys mind turning around while I
change into something
more comfortable good?
Yeah, sure I don't mind
changing like right now
Have you ever met a
woman who's that daring?
Hey, what do you say we turn
around and see if she's done yet?
Good idea. Eh, oh.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I'm doing business, of course.
Use your heads, guys.
I'm a thief who only targets pirates,
and my next score is this ship.
I never said anything about
being a member of this crew.
I was just traveling with them.
Nothing more.
Even though I only spent a short
time with Luffy and the gang,
I sure had a lot of fun.
Make sure to tell them that I said.
If it's truly meant to be,
I'll see them real soon.
Hey, where are you going?
We're gonna be in so much trouble!
Our only job was to look after the ship,
and you're making us fail miserably!
So that's the story of how big
Sizznami took the ship. Sorry.
Damn it!
She just had to make
a bad situation worse.
The Heartless Thief kind
of gave us that ship.
Wait!
I see a ship!
It's the Going Mary!
Tell me where your boat is.
We have it moored to the restaurant.
Saru and Usopp don't just stand there.
Take their ship and go get Nami.
Calm down.
Let her keep the ship.
Trust me, that woman is way
more trouble than she's worth.
She's the only person I'll
accept as the ship's navigator.
Fine, I'll do it.
One high-maintenance
captain, you know that.
All right, Usopp, let's go.
Okay.
The ship's ready for action, Big Bro Zoro!
Hey, what about you?
I should probably stick around here till I
get this thing settled
with the restaurant,
know what I mean?
Well, be careful.
The situation here could
get really bad really fast.
Yeah, got that right.
The ship has been broken to splinters!
Over there! It's that man!
He came back!
Don Krieg!
The man who destroyed our fleet is back!
What are we gonna do?
That's... that's him.
That man is.
That son of a bitch.
But Psycho Fold is back here!
He's gonna kill us all!
Everybody's gonna die.
Hey?
Who's that?
That's the man I've been looking for.
Hawkeye. Mihawk.
So that's Mihawk.
Yeah, the greatest swordsman.
That's got to be the guy
who destroyed Krieg's fleet.
He sunk 50 pirate ships out on
the Grand Line all by himself.
Looks like he came back to finish
the job, but is that all he wants?
Wait a minute.
He just looks like any ordinary man.
He doesn't even appear to have any
kind of special weapons with him.
He carries his weapon on his back.
That's impossible!
He couldn't have destroyed a galleon
like that using nothing but a sword.
Hawkeye Mihawk is a true master.
He is without a doubt the
greatest swordsman in the world.
You...
you monster!
Why are you doing this to us?
What the hell have we ever done to you?
Just killing time.
Bastard!
What? I missed?
But I aimed straight for him.
He diverted them.
He changed the course of the
bullets using the tip of his sword.
That can't be.
Hold on who do you think you are?
I've never seen a sword handled
so gently, but with such grace
There's no strength in
swordplay based on force
Did you also use that sword
to slice up this ship?
I did
Then it's true.
You're the best.
He's got three swords.
It couldn't be I set sail for
only one reason to meet you and
What is your goal to beat you?
Heh, how foolish.
They sure were nice guys,
but I wonder, well, I wonder if
they would let me join them again.
I hope I see them.
Free.
I just want to be free.
I'm sorry, Bellamere.
You've got spare time, so let's do this.
Whoa, no way! It's him!
Rowan, Noah and Zoro!
It's Zoro of the Three Swords Tile! It is?
Really?
A pirate hunter?
He's a what?
Hey Luffy we better hurry come on
the going mary is about to sell
right out of sight Hey Luffy a
fight you're a weak pitiful creature
If you are in fact a competent
swordsman you should see the
disparity in our abilities even
Before we cross swords I must
ask you why have you challenged
me could it be your courage or
Is it simply your ignorance my
ambition drives me also I made a
promise I intend to keep the
Greatest swordsman in the world
going up against robo no azoro
two masters of swordplay what kind
Of a fight is this gonna turn out
to be there isn't a person alive
who can defeat big bro he's It's
already the best in the world!
Funny.
What do you think you're
gonna do with that?
It'll be more than adequate.
After all, you wouldn't kill a
fly with a cannon, would you?
You may have quite the
reputation on the East Blue,
but that doesn't mean much to me.
This sea is by far the
weakest of the four.
Unfortunately, I don't carry any
blades smaller than this one.
I have had just about
enough of your attitude.
Now you die!
You have no idea how
big the world really is.
Onigiri!
What the...?
Saru!
What?
Big Bro's onigiri was stopped?
But that's crazy!
That attack never fails to stop an enemy!
What's going on here?
I can't move my swords.
What has he done?
No one's been able to defend
against that technique.
He stopped it with a pocket knife.
No, this can't be happening.
He can't be this much better than me.
There's no way our skills
are this far apart.
I am not that far behind
the world's strongest!
You're just toying with them, right?
Fight for real, Big Bro! Big Bro!
You can't be that much better than me!
Such ferocious swordplay.
How can he defend against Zoro's
three-sword style with such a small knife?
He's more of a monster with a
blade than even the Great Zoro!
I did not devote my entire
life to swordsmanship
to be dispatched by a toy like this!
You're lucky, Zoro.
Being born as a man.
All I ever wanted was to be
the world's greatest swordsman.
Promise me!
Promise me that someday one of us will
be the world's greatest swordsman!
We'll see who gets there!
It's a promise!
To become the world's strongest!
I ask that you let me have that sword!
I'm gonna get stronger than she ever was!
Strong enough that my name
reaches up to the heavens!
I am going to be the
world's greatest swordsman!
I promised her.
I promised.
I will defeat this man. For her.
What is it then?
What weight do you carry
upon your shoulders?
Speak up, weakling!
We're deeply impressed by your skills.
Would you let us join you?
We're the famed bounty
hunting duo that's fearsome
enough to silence a
crying child by a hair.
Yosaku and Johnny.
How dare you call him weakling!
You'll pay for that!
We'll teach you a lesson!
No! Yosaku! Johnny!
Get back here!
Stay put!
No, I won't lose.
I refuse to be defeated.
Tiger?
World's greatest swordsman.
Sounds pretty good.
The King of the Pirates wouldn't have
any less than the best on his crew.
Trap!
you are defeated yet you won't
step back why not but i will not run
even if i retreat a single I would
be shattering the promises I've made.
I can't run.
I would lose my honor.
You see, without that, there
would be nothing left for me here.
That's what defeat is.
Then I won't accept defeat.
Then you'll die.
I'd rather die than give up.
A strong heart indeed.
He chooses death before defeat.
Sir, state your name.
I am Roan O 'Zoro.
I'll remember it.
No one as strong as you has
come around in quite some time.
So as a swordsman's courtesy,
I'll use the world's strongest
black sword to finish you.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Look!
He took it out!
That's the sword that sliced up the ship!
So this is it.
Will it be the world's strongest or death?
Enough, big bro!
Stop it, please!
Three-sword style secret technique!
Fall!
3,000 worlds!
I've lost.
Never in my life did I imagine I'd lose.
So this is the power of
the greatest in the world.
But why?
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame.
Fine.
You shouldn't rush
these things, young man.
Zoro!
Be probable!
No!
Why?
I devoted my entire life to becoming
the world's greatest swordsman.
It was my choice, so I'm the only
one who gets to call me stupid.
He's insane.
His opponent was way out of his league.
How this fight would end
was clear from the start.
Why choose death?
Don't be stupid!
Give up your ambition and live!
So this is the power of the
Grand Line. It's terrifying.
The pirate hunter Zoro was as
helpless as a newborn baby.
Damn you!
Big bro!
He must be some kind of freak!
So that loudmouthed little twerp
has the power of a Devil Fruit.
Are you that young warrior's comrade?
I'm impressed with you
for not interfering.
There's nothing to be upset about.
Your friend will live.
Big bro, say something, please! Zoro!
Zoro!
Come on, let's hurry up and
get him out of the water.
I've got some medicine. Here!
It's still far too early for you to die.
My name is Hawkeye Mihawk.
You're strong, but there
is much for you to learn.
No matter how many years it takes,
I will hold this title as the greatest
in the world and wait for you.
Until that day, you must hone your skills.
Then, seek me out, Roronoa Zoro!
Please say something! Anything!
Not just anyone can earn the
regard of Hawkeye Mihawk.
You.
What is your goal?
To be the king.
Your ambitions are even
loftier than your friends.
That's quite a task.
Yeah, well, you just
let me worry about that.
He's alive!
He was just unconscious. Big Ro!
If you're alive, then say something!
Zoro!
Big Ro!
Luffy!
Can you hear me?
Yeah!
I'm sorry for disappointing you.
I know that you need nothing less than
the greatest swordsman in the world.
I've let you down.
Please forgive me.
Okay, okay!
You can stop saying things now!
Bro!
I solemnly swear, from this moment
forward, that I will never lose again!
Until the day comes when I
defeat him and take his title!
I will never, never be defeated!
Is that okay, King of the Pirates?
Yep.
You're a good team.
I hope to see you again someday.
Hey, Hawkeye!
I was under the impression that
you had come here to take my life.
Weren't you here to kill Don
Krieg, ruler of the East Blue?
The thought had crossed my mind,
but I've had enough fun for today,
so I'm going home to get some rest.
I don't care if you've had enough.
I haven't even gotten started.
Um, but, sir...
Maybe it's not a good idea
to try to keep him here.
Now it's time to die!
He just won't learn, will he?
Goddamn, he escaped!
Who's up?
Luffy!
Go on ahead!
I'll leave Nami to you! Roger that!
Don't you worry about a thing!
Zoro and I are gonna get her right back!
And make sure you get that
cook to join our crew!
And then, on the Going Merry, the five
of us will set sail to the Grand Line!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
All right, Ben.
We ran into a little distraction from
our plan, but the real fight starts now.
We're gonna take that ship! Yes, sir!
Hey, Pops!
Can I stop doing these chores if
I get those pirates out of here?
Search yourself.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me!
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever changes,
I call out your name?
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream. You